# **Anyi Jaramillo**

LinkedIn | GitHub | HackerRank

Location: Medellín, Colombia Email: anyi.jar@gmail.com | Phone: +57 3182168434

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

I am a highly skilled front-end developer and bioengineer with +3 years of experience in React, Vue, Typescript, HTML and CSS preprocessors. I have knowledge and also worked with technologies such as Angular, Node.js, REST APIs and .NET.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Fron-end : Typescript, Javascript, Vue, Vuex, Vuetify, React.js, Angular, HTML, CSS, SaSS, PostCSS, Webpack

**Back-end** : C#, .Net, Node.js

: Jest, Testing Library, Playwright **Testing** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Front-end Developer**

May 2022 - Aug 2023

Azkoyen Group

Remote - Peralta, Navarre, Spain

- Development and maintenance of telemetry applications developed with Typescript, Vue.js and .Net
- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from Cosmos databases
- Designing and implementing a mobile-first user interface that is optimized for different devices and screen sizes

#### **Front-end Developer**

Nov 2020 - May 2022

Corunet

Remote - A Coruña, Galicia, Spain

- Minimalist application development for Zara's sales department made with Typescritp, React.js, Angular and
- · Testing with React Testing Library and Jest
- · Hight adherence to the Figma application design

## **Front-end Developer**

Jun 2020 - Nov 2020

Lantia SAS

Remote - Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

- Development of a search of patents with **React**
- Development of web animations with Javascript and CSS to Moodle course
- Support to add to the frontend application React with Hooks

## **Software Developer**

Apr 2020 - Jun 2020

Freelancer

Remote - Galicia Spain

• Development of an educational management platform

#### **EDUCATION**

Lemoncode

Málaga, Málaga, Spain Sep 2022 - Present

Master Front-End

Málaga, Málaga, Spain

University of Málaga Artificial intelligence course - Samsung DEV - Spain

Apr 2021 - Jul 2021

**Hack a Boss** 

A Coruña, A Coruña, Spain Sep 2019 - Mar 2020

Bootcamp Full-Stack Javascript

Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia Sep 2007 - Mar 2016

**University of Antioquia** Degree in Bioengineering

## Virtual tutor - Bootcamp backend .Net

Jul 2023 – Sep 2023

PionerasDev and Women Who Code Medellín

- Mentored aspiring developers in the .NET Bootcamp, providing guidance and support throughout the program
- Assisted participants in understanding and applying .NET concepts, troubleshooting code, and fostering a collaborative learning environment

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Front-end Developer Samsung DEV Spain and Bejob
- Basic Javascript HackerRank
- Typescript Fundamentals Platzi
- English B2 EF